http://www.ultimateinsurancejobs.com/privacy-policy/

Skip to main content
-->
Privacy Policy
Information Automatically Logged
This site uses your IP address to help diagnose problems with our server and to administer our site.
This site records the browser type to monitor market penetration of various web browsers so we can better determine the Internet technologies we may utilize in the design of our pages.
This site uses page referrer data - that is, information about the page that linked you to this page - to determine to what extent our page is referenced by other resources on the Web.
This data may be used to preserve the integrity of our computing resources.
Personal Information
This site collects name and contact information, education and work history, as well as other work preferences.
This information is used to advertise insurance candidates to insurance employers. E-mail address is used to send occassional promotional e-mails if the candidate chooses to opt in.
We share contact information only with insurance employers.
A user may set their resume to be confidential so that an employer may contact them via a form on our site, but the candidates name, address, e-mail address and phone number are kept confidential.
A user may access the "My Resume" function from the candidate homepage where they may change any of their personal information.
Cookies
This site stores the users login information whenever a user chooses to have the site remember them, so they do not have to login each time they return to the site.
GreatJobSpot.com, GreatJaxJobs.com, TBJobs.com, GreatFloridaJobs.com, SFLJobs.com, GreatCasinoJobs.com, GreatAutomobileJobs.com, GvilleJobs.com, OrlandoJobs.com, GreatInsuranceJobs.com, GreatInsuranceRecruiters.com, UltimateInsuranceJobs.com and InsuranceSalesJobs.com may access this information.
These cookies are saved until 30 days from date of login
This website uses the Google AdWords remarketing service to advertise on third party websites (including Google) to previous visitors to our site. It could mean that we advertise to previous visitors who haven’t completed a task on our site, for example not filing out a job application. This could be in the form of an advertisement on the Google search results page, or a site in the Google Display Network. Third-party vendors, including Google, use cookies to serve ads based on someone’s past visits to the [CLIENT NAME] website. Of course, any data collected will be used in accordance with our own privacy policy and Google’s privacy policy.
You can set preferences for how Google advertises to you using the Google Ad Preferences page, and if you want to you can
opt out of interest-based advertising entirely by cookie settings or permanently using a browser plugin.
Session Management
Session variables on our web server are used to manage sessions.
This site uses session variables which contains the candidate's ID for that candidate in our database so that candidates may apply for jobs.
The session information used by this site is deleted when your browser is closed.
Security
This site has security measures in place to protect the loss, misuse, and alteration of the information under our control. Log file access is restricted to system administrators while stored on the server. Log files are rotated regularly and archived in a secure location.
Note: User and password information is not encrypted before it is transmitted across the network.
Contact Information
If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this site, you may contact us.
